const question1 = [
	{
		question: '2 + 5 = ?',
		answers: ['7','5','3','4'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '4 + 5 = ?',
		answers: ['8','9','10','11'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '2 + 8 = ?',
		answers: ['8','11','10','9'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '7 + 3 = ?',
		answers: ['11','8','9','10'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '6 + 9 = ?',
		answers: ['15','12','13','14'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '8 + 4 = ?',
		answers: ['15','12','13','14'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '7 + 9 = ?',
		answers: ['15','12','16','14'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '7 + 7 = ?',
		answers: ['15','12','13','14'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '8 + 9 = ?',
		answers: ['17','19','15','16'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '9 + 5 = ?',
		answers: ['18','14','15','16'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
const question2 = [
	{
		question: '5 - 2 = ?',
		answers: ['3','2','1','4'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '9 - 6 = ?',
		answers: ['4','3','2','5'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '8 - 3 = ?',
		answers: ['6','4','5','7'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '7 - 3 = ?',
		answers: ['5','6','7','4'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '9 - 6 = ?',
		answers: ['3','1','2','4'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '8 - 4 = ?',
		answers: ['5','4','3','1'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '15 - 6 = ?',
		answers: ['8','10','9','11'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '14 - 7 = ?',
		answers: ['5','8','6','7'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '17 - 9 = ?',
		answers: ['8','9','7','10'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '15 - 9 = ?',
		answers: ['8','6','5','4'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
const question3 = [
	{
		question: '2 x 3 = ?',
		answers: ['6','8','5','4'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '4 x 3 = ?',
		answers: ['15','12','13','14'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '2 x 9 = ?',
		answers: ['15','16','18','14'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '5 x 3 = ?',
		answers: ['14','12','13','15'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '2 x 5 = ?',
		answers: ['10','9','8','12'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '4 x 5 = ?',
		answers: ['22','20','18','16'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '2 x 8 = ?',
		answers: ['18','10','16','14'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '7 x 3 = ?',
		answers: ['11','18','19','21'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '8 x 3 = ?',
		answers: ['24','29','25','26'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '5 x 5 = ?',
		answers: ['28','25','24','26'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
const question4 = [
	{
		question: '6 : 2 = ?',
		answers: ['3','6','5','4'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '16 : 4 = ?',
		answers: ['3','4','2','1'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '18 : 2 = ?',
		answers: ['5','6','9','7'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '15 : 3 = ?',
		answers: ['4','2','3','5'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '10 : 2 = ?',
		answers: ['5','9','8','6'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '18 : 9 = ?',
		answers: ['3','2','4','1'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '16 : 8 = ?',
		answers: ['1','3','2','4'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '21 : 7 = ?',
		answers: ['2','4','5','3'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '24 : 3 = ?',
		answers: ['8','7','5','6'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '25 : 5 = ?',
		answers: ['8','5','4','6'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
const question5 = [
	{
		question: '25 + 13 = ?',
		answers: ['38','48','37','39'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '34 + 55 = ?',
		answers: ['88','89','99','98'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '42 + 26 = ?',
		answers: ['69','67','68','78'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '45 + 33 = ?',
		answers: ['77','79','88','78'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '52 + 28 = ?',
		answers: ['80','70','81','71'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '74 + 16 = ?',
		answers: ['91','90','80','89'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '29 + 58 = ?',
		answers: ['77','85','87','86'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '37 + 45 = ?',
		answers: ['83','72','81','82'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '75 + 17 = ?',
		answers: ['92','82','93','91'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '25 + 68 = ?',
		answers: ['92','93','91','83'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
const question6 = [
	{
		question: '95 - 41 = ?',
		answers: ['54','44','55','53'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '84 - 23 = ?',
		answers: ['62','61','51','60'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '67 - 34 = ?',
		answers: ['34','32','33','43'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '59 - 45 = ?',
		answers: ['15','13','24','14'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '33 - 12 = ?',
		answers: ['21','20','31','22'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '74 - 38 = ?',
		answers: ['35','36','27','46'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '58 - 39 = ?',
		answers: ['29','18','19','28'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '93 - 29 = ?',
		answers: ['75','74','65','64'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '34 - 27 = ?',
		answers: ['7','8','17','6'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '60 - 17 = ?',
		answers: ['42','43','53','52'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
const question7 = [
	{
		question: '8 x 9 = ?',
		answers: ['72','71','73','82'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '7 x 8 = ?',
		answers: ['57','56','65','66'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '9 x 7 = ?',
		answers: ['62','64','63','54'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '6 x 8 = ?',
		answers: ['47','58','49','48'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '6 x 7 = ?',
		answers: ['42','41','52','43'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '17 x 5 = ?',
		answers: ['75','85','95','86'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '7 x 13 = ?',
		answers: ['92','81','91','90'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '9 x 11 = ?',
		answers: ['98','89','88','99'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '6 x 15 = ?',
		answers: ['90','80','85','95'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '12 x 8 = ?',
		answers: ['92','96','86','106'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
const question8 = [
	{
		question: '45 : 9 = ?',
		answers: ['5','4','6','7'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '81 : 9 = ?',
		answers: ['10','9','8','7'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '63 : 7 = ?',
		answers: ['7','8','9','6'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '72 : 8 = ?',
		answers: ['8','7','10','9'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '56 : 7 = ?',
		answers: ['8','10','9','7'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '85 : 17 = ?',
		answers: ['4','5','7','6'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '87 : 29 = ?',
		answers: ['2','4','3','5'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '93 : 31 = ?',
		answers: ['5','4','6','3'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '92 : 4 = ?',
		answers: ['23','24','22','33'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '72 : 18 = ?',
		answers: ['2','4','3','5'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
const question9 = [
	{
		question: '45 : 9 = ?',
		answers: ['5','4','6','7'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '81 : 9 = ?',
		answers: ['10','9','8','7'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '63 : 7 = ?',
		answers: ['7','8','9','6'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{
		question: '72 : 8 = ?',
		answers: ['8','7','10','9'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '56 : 7 = ?',
		answers: ['8','10','9','7'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '85 : 17 = ?',
		answers: ['4','5','7','6'],
		correct: 1
	},
	{
		question: '87 : 29 = ?',
		answers: ['2','4','3','5'],
		correct: 2
	},
	{ 
		question: '93 : 31 = ?',
		answers: ['5','4','6','3'],
		correct: 3
	},
	{
		question: '92 : 4 = ?',
		answers: ['23','24','22','33'],
		correct: 0
	},
	{
		question: '72 : 18 = ?',
		answers: ['2','4','3','5'],
		correct: 1
	},
]
group_question = [question1,question2,question3,question4,question5];
// questions = [];
// for(i = 0;i < 5; i++){
// 	var min = 0;
// 	var max = 9;
// 	var random_int = Math.floor(Math.random()*(max-min+1)+min);
// 	questions.push(group_question[i][random_int]);
// }
class altp {
	constructor(file){
		this.ui = new ui();
		this.questions = [];
		for(var i = 0;i < 5; i++){
			var min = 0;
			var max = 9;
			var random_int = Math.floor(Math.random()*(max-min+1)+min);
			this.questions.push(group_question[i][random_int]);
		}
		this.ui.ShowScreen("welcome_screen");
		this.current_question = 0;
		this.current_answer = null;
    
		this.background_sound = new sound('bg(02).mp3');
		this.start_sound = new sound('start(07).mp3');
		this.wait_answer_sound = new sound('wait_answer(25).mp3');
		this.question_bg_sound = new sound('question_bg(06).mp3');
		this.correct_sound = new sound('correct(21).mp3');
		this.wrong_sound = new sound('wrong(22).mp3');

		// this.background_sound.StartMusic();
		this.ui.OnStartButtonClick( () => {
			this.StartGame();
		});
	}
	StartGame(){
		this.ui.ShowScreen('question_screen');
		this.ui.ResetAnswerStyle();
		// this.background_sound.StopMusic();
		this.start_sound.StartMusic( () => {

			this.question_bg_sound.StartMusic();
		});
		this.ui.ShowQuestion(this.questions[this.current_question],this.current_question);
		var choosed = false;
		this.ui.OnClickAnswer( (answer) => {
			// console.log(checkchoose);
			if(choosed == false){
				choosed = true;
				this.current_answer = answer;
				this.ui.SetSelectedAnswer(answer);
				this.start_sound.StopMusic();
				this.start_sound = new sound('start(07).mp3');
				this.question_bg_sound.StopMusic();
				this.question_bg_sound = new sound('question_bg(06).mp3')
				this.wait_answer_sound.StartMusic( () => {
					this.CheckAnswer();
				});
			}
		});
	}
	CheckAnswer(){
		if(this.current_answer == this.questions[this.current_question].correct){
			this.ui.ShowResult(this.current_answer,this.questions[this.current_question].correct);
			this.correct_sound.StartMusic( () => {
				this.current_question++;
				if(this.current_question==5){
					this.ui.ShowScreen('win_screen');
					this.ui.ShowWinScreen();
					this.ui.OnWinButtonClick( () => {
						this.Reset();
					});
				}
				else{
					// console.log(this.current_question);
					this.ui.ShowScreen('congratulation_screen');
					this.ui.ShowCongratulationScreen(this.current_question);
					this.ui.OnContinueButtonClick( (current_question) => {
						this.StartGame();
					});
					// this.StartGame();
				}
			});
		}
		else{
			this.ui.ShowResult(this.current_answer,this.questions[this.current_question].correct);
			this.wrong_sound.StartMusic( () => {
				this.ui.ShowScreen('lose_screen');
				this.ui.ShowLoseScreen();
				this.ui.OnResetButtonClick( () => {
					this.Reset();
				});
			});
		}
	}
	// ResetMusic(){
		// this.background_sound.MusicStop();
		// this.start_sound.MusicStop();
		// this.wait_answer_sound.MusicStop();
		// this.question_bg_sound.MusicStop();
		// this.correct_sound.MusicStop();
		// this.wrong_sound.MusicStop();
	// }
	Reset(){
		// this.ResetMusic();

		this.current_question = 0;
		this.ui.ResetAnswerStyle();
		this.ui.ShowScreen('welcome_screen');
		this.questions=[];
		for(var i = 0;i < 5; i++){
			var min = 0;
			var max = 9;
			var random_int = Math.floor(Math.random()*(max-min+1)+min);
			this.questions.push(group_question[i][random_int]);
		}
	}
}
var game = new altp();